That's the age-old conundrum. Like, are
you investing in Elon and his vision for
10 or 15 years down the road for putting
people on Mars and transforming AI, or
are you just looking at this expensive
stock that doesn't make any money?
>> How big of a factor does he play into
this entire investment decision for our
viewers?
>> I think he's the factor. Especially with
an innovation company that's not
profitable, that's still probably 10, 15
years from really achieving its final
vision or form, you're really making a
bet on the person and betting on Elon in
the past has been an extremely lucrative
proposition, whether you got in on Tesla
in 2010 at some point. If you did, you
know, I hope your yacht is nice. Good to
see you.
>> Do the Elon fanboys just go, "Well, this
is the old toy, and now we want to go to
the new toy." Is there a potential for
an acquisition, and then we get into
this idea of an Elon conglomerate
company?
>> If Tesla has historically been a bet on
Elon, and there's a fresher bet on Elon,
and there's honestly more stuff under
the hood of SpaceX, it'll be more of a
pure-play AI company than Tesla because
it has xAI. So, let's imagine that
happens. Tesla starts to fall out of
favor. Maybe people are even funding
their SpaceX purchases by selling Tesla.
But, I'm going to drop the hammer here.
>> Ooh.
>> And I'm just going to say, what if they
merge? What if there's one big Elon
conglomerate that's Tesla and SpaceX
combined, and that's not just me saying
BS? Like, this definitely something
that's been out in the thirds been
something that's been rumored.
>> Yeah.
>> And
I think it would really address a lot of
this like this risk that you're seeing
if there's two separate entities that
kind of are both pegged to Elon.
>> Yeah, I mean, look, there's only so much
money these Elon fans have to invest.
So, ultimately, they're going to have to
make a decision, and just making it Elon
Inc., right, and letting everyone buy in
on SpaceX, I think that makes a lot of
sense. The flip side is, and you know, I
think this is a lot of the criticism
heading into
for the Tesla merger, is that it becomes
this kind of Frankenstein company,
right?
>> It's going to be awesome, and as a
Markets Reporter, I can't wait. You
know, my mouth is watering at the
prospect of an Elon Musk Frankenstein
entity.